aoi hoshi ni senritsu ga hashiru
a
o
i
ho
shi
ni
se
n
ri
tsu
ga
ha
shi
ru
A shudder runs over the blue planet
푸른 지구에 전율이 흐른다
kuroi arashi chikazuku toki
ku
ro
i
a
ra
shi
chi
ka
zu
ku
to
ki
It's the time the dark storm approaches
검은 폭풍이 닥쳐오는 순간
kokoro no oku de mezameru HERO
ko
ro
no
o
ku
de
me
za
ru
HE
RO
It's as if a hero is awakening on the inside
마음 속의 눈을 뜬 영웅들이여
tobitatsu no da furimukazu ni
to
bi
ta
tsu
no
da
fu
ri
mu
ka
zu
ni
Fly away and don't look back!
뒤돌아보지 말고 날아가라
DAGWON kagayake DAGWON
DA
G
WON
ka
ga
ya
ke
DA
G
WON
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Brave Command Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Dagwon... Shine on!! Dagwon!
다그온 빛나라!! 다그온
heiwa mamoru namae sa
he
i
wa
ma
mo
ru
na
ma
e
sa
The name that protects the peace
평화를 지키는 이름이다
DAGWON oretachi DAGWON
DA
G
WON
o
re
ta
chi
DA
G
WON
Dagwon! We are Dagwon!
다그온 우리는 다그온
yume wa zettai watasanai
yu
me
wa
ze
t
ta
i
wa
ta
sa
na
i
We will never hand over our dream
꿈은 절대로 넘겨줄 수 없다
afureru yuuki te ni shitai nara
a
fu
re
ru
yu
u
ki
te
ni
shi
ta
i
na
ra
To grab the overflowing courage
넘쳐흐르는 용기를 거머쥐고 싶다면
tsuyoku tsuyoku yuujou shinjiru koto sa
tsu
yo
ku
tsu
yo
ku
yu
u
jo
shi
n
ji
ru
ko
to
sa
We believe in our friendship firmly
우리 우정을 굳게 믿는 거다
kizutsuku koto mo osore wa shinai
ki
zu
tsu
ku
ko
to
mo
o
so
re
wa
shi
na
i
We are not afraid of getting hurt
상처입는 것도 두렵지 않아
mugendai no mirai wo egaku sono tame ni
mu
ge
n
da
i
no
mi
ra
i
wo
e
ga
ku
so
no
ta
me
ni
In order to reach that infinite future!
무한대의 미래를 그려내기 위해서라면
Brutal aliens escaped from the Space Prison Sargasso.
우주 감옥 사르갓소의 흉악한 우주인들
To protect the Earth from those evil hands, Brave Dagwon fights on to this day.
그 마수로부터 지구를 지키기 위해 오늘도 계속해서 싸우는 용자 다그온
Now, a new member has been dispatched from the Space Police Organization; his name is Thunder Rai.
그들에게 지금 우주 경찰 기구에서 파견된 새로운 멤버, 선더 라이가 가담했다
The Three Warugaia Brothers are the most cruel gang of space criminals in Sargasso.
와르가이아 3형제는 사르갓소 내에서 가장 잔인한 우주 범죄자 일당입니다
The one who appeared last time is the youngest one, Hido.
이번에 모습을 드러낸 것은 동생인 히도
And the other two brothers are named Mado and Gedo.
그리고 녀석에겐 마도, 게도라는 두 형이 있습니다
I see. That's why you were calling them the Three Warugaia Brothers.
그렇군, 그래서 와르가이아 3형제란 말이구나
Yes. I heard that many comrades of the Space Police Organization had been sacrificed to arrest them.
네, 녀석들을 체포하기 위해 수많은 우주 경찰의 동료들이 희생되었다고 들었습니다
Hey, hey, are you kidding?
이봐 이봐, 정말이냐
To know that such guys took Sargasso...
그런 녀석들이 사르갓소를 장악했다니…
The Three Warugaia Brothers...
와르가이아 3형제…
Those guys will rule lots of space prisoners and challenge us.
녀석들은 수많은 우주 죄수를 지배하애 두고 틀림없이 우리 다그온에게 도전해올 거야
Who do you plan to send to Earth this time?
이번엔 어느 녀석을 지구에 보낼 거야?
If you like, let me choose!
뭐하면 내가 고를게
I hope I can, Mado bro!
응, 괜찮지, 마도 형?
You may not use your head.
고를 필요 없어
I've already chosen the next assassin.
다음 자객은 이미 정해두었다
The one that's best suited to take out those Dagwon punks.
다그온을 끌어내기에 가장 적합한 녀석을 말이야
It's you, Trucker Seijin!
너다, 트럭커 성인!
Chase the Ghost Truck!
유령 트럭을 쫓아라!
Runaway Alien Trucker Seijin
Appears
폭주 우주인 트럭커 성인
등장
This guy, that guy, they're all idiots!
이놈도 저놈도 바보들 뿐이구만~
It's so awesome! Speed up more!
대단해, 짱이야~
좀 더 밟아봐~
Alright!
좋았어~
What are you doing, you-
무슨 짓이야, 이자식!
Hey! You!
야 이놈아!
What?!
아니?!
You're late.
드디어 왔구나
We were waiting for you.
가다리고 있었어~
Sorry to make you wait.
오래 기다리셨습니다…
What?!
뭐야?!
Ms. Maria went out with Rai?!
마리아 씨가 라이 녀석이랑 같이 나갔다고?!
It's about a ghost truck this time.
이번엔 유령 트럭이라더군
That occult girl always likes weird things.
여전히 별난 걸 좋아하는 오컬트 소녀라니까
Why, Ms. Maria?!
너무하십니다, 마리아 씨!
Why?! Why didn't you tell me about this?
어째서!
어째서 내겐 한마디도…
Why did you pick such a rookie...
왜 하필이면 그런 풋내기하고…
Rai has a motorcycle.
라이는 오토바이 갖고 있잖아
I have a bicycle, though!
나도 자전거는 가지고 있어!
Idiot.
바~보
Do you think you can catch up to a truck with that?
자전거로 트럭을 쫓을 셈이냐?
Damn! Rai, you damn brat!
젠자~앙! 라이 녀석!
How dare you take Maria before your senpai!
이 선배님을 제치고 마리아 씨와~!
Are you a kid?
니가 애냐…
A ghost truck, you say?
유령 트럭 말입니까?
Right. According to a witness, nobody was in the driver's seat.
그래, 목격자의 말로는 그 트럭의 운전석에는 아무도 타고 있지 않았대
A traffic violation at the very least!
교통 위반이라니, 정말 최악이야
It's told that many police cars were damaged because it destroyed the cars nearby.
주변의 자동차를 거리낌없이 날려 버리고 파괴해서 경찰차도 벌써 몇 대나 피해를 입었대
It's absolutely a spiritual phenomenon.
틀림없이 심령 현상이야
Could the spirit of a person who's dead be accidentally driving that car?
사고 같은 걸로 죽은 사람의 자박령이 운전하고 있는 걸까
Or did a spirit take over the truck itself?
아니면 트럭 자체레 영이 씌여서 도로를 헤매이고 있는 걸까
Anyway, that's what we have to find out.
어쨌든 조사해 봐야지
Oh dear...
이런 이런…
That was dangerous!
위험했어
What kind of driver is he?!
뭐 저련 녀석이 다 있어!
Oh, that must be the ghost truck!
아앗, 혹시 저게 그 유령 트럭?
What?! Rai, let's follow it!
뭐라고?! 라이, 쫓아가자!
Ye- yeah!
아, 네!
Nobody's there as expected!
역시 사람이 없어!
You must be Trucker Seijin!
네녀석은, 트럭커 성인!
Stop!
기다려!
Thunder Throttle!
선더 슬롯!
Wait! What can we do if you drop us off here?!
잠깐! 이런 곳에 내려놓다니, 무슨 생각이야?!
I feel lighter now.
이걸로 가벼워졌군
He just left...
가 버렸네…
Rai, you idiot!
라이, 이 바보~!
Why do I have to track that ghost truck too?!
왜 나까지 유령 트럭을 찾아야 하는 거냐?!
Let Rai and Maria do that!
나 참, 라이와 마리아에게 맡기면 되잖아
What if something happens to Ms. Maria?! I am worried about that!
마리아 씨에게 무슨 일이 생기면 어떡하냐?! 난 그걸 걱정하고 있는 거라구!
Oh, weren't you actually worried about Rai and Maria becoming friends?
호오~ 사실 걱정되는 건 라이와 마리아가 친해지면 어쩌나 하는 게 아니더냐~
Geki?
게~키?
A recruit alien detective and a occult girl...
우주인 신참 형사와 오컬트 소녀라…
They might go well together!
그럭저럭 어울릴지도 모르겠는데?
They don't! No way!
전혀 안 어울려!
How dare you say that!
헛소리를 지껄이다니, 이자식!
Hey, get off me! It's dangerous!
어어, 붙지마
위험하잖아, 짜식아!
What the?!
뭐야?!
-Hey, there's no driver in that truck!
-En, let's follow it!
이봐, 저 트럭, 사람이 없었어! -엔, 쫓아가자!
-오우!
Senpai!
선배~!
I'm sorry!
죄송합니다~
Rai?!
-라이?!
-We're going, too!
-Yeah!
-우리도 쫓아가자!
-응!
Senpai, the true identity of the ghost truck is that of an alien!
선배, 유령 트럭의 정체는 우주인입니다
What?!
뭐야?!
It is Trucker Seijin from Sargasso.
녀석은 사르갓소의 트럭커 성인입니다
Trucker Seijin?!
트럭커 성인?!
Alright. Leave it to us!
좋아, 우리에게 맡겨 두라구!
Go, En! Full acceleration!
가라, 엔!
엑셀 전개다!
How's this?!
어떠냐?!
Oh, dammit! We got ahead of it!
아이구 이런, 앞질러 버렸다
You idiot! We got ahead, so now what?!
바보놈아, 앞질러서 뭐할려고?!
Darn you...
이자식…
Don't underestimate Fire Stratus!
파이어 스투라투스를 얕보지 마라!
Spark Flash!
스파크 플래시!
Look at yourself!
꼴좋다!
You idiot!
바보녀석~
Do you think a truck can drive on such rough ground?
그런 거친 땅에서 트럭이 달릴 수 있을 것 같냐!
What?!
아니?!
Did it evolute...
진화한 건가…
Damn, you're not getting away!
젠장, 안 놓친다!
I'll follow it too!
우리도 쫓아가자!
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Original Korean Subtitles by Jaebari (재바리)
Translated to English by Subdivers
Checked by Great Exkaiser103
자막 원본(번역): 재바리
수정: Subdivers
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
We found you!
찾았다!
A truck, and now ADV?
트럭에 이어 ADV가 폭주하다니…
It came!
왔구나!
Large truck over there!
거기 대형 차량!
Stop at the sidemost lane!
왼쪽에 기대어 멈추시오!
Stop! I told you to stop!
멈춰! 멈추라고!
Stop!
멈춰줘…
Why does it keep running?
어째서 녀석은 달리기만 하는 거지?
Why... Alright!
어째서… 좋아!
Try Dagwon!
트라이 다그온
Thunder Rai!
선더 라이
Thunder Eagle Attack!
선더 이글 어택!
Senpai!
선배!
Great job, Rai! Leave the rest to us!
좋았어, 라이!
뒤는 우리에게 맡겨라!
We almost got it! We'll finish this at once!
따라잡았다
단숨에 끝장내 주마!
Wait. There are some cars that couldn't escape yet.
기다려, 도망치지 못한 자동차가 있어
What?!
뭐야?!
Look out!
위험해!
It stopped!
멈췄잖아?!
It transformed?!
변형한 건가?!
Merging Fusion!
융합합체
(融合合體)
Dag Turbo!
다그 터보
Merging Fusion!
융합합체
(融合合體)
Dag Armor!
다그 아머
Merging Fusion!
융합합체
(融合合體)
Dag Wing!
다그 윙
Dag Wing, save the people on the bridge first!
다그 윙은 다리 위의 사람들을 구해!
Roger that!
알았습니다!
Our power isn't enough!
둘만으로는 힘이 부족해!
We must endure!
어떻게든 버텨야 해!
Merging Fusion!
융합합체
(融合合體)
Dag Drill!
다그 드릴
Endure a bit more! With your guts!
조금만 더 버텨!
근성을 넣으라구! -오우!
-오우!
Senpai!
선배!
Rai, you go follow that guy!
라이, 당신은 녀석을 쫓으세요!
Roger that!
알았습니다!
It won't end like this...
이대론 끝이 나지 않아
Let's go!
간다…!
Merging Fusion!
융합합체
(融合合體)
Dag Thunder!
다그 선더
What?!
아니?!
Trucker Seijin can evolve to a stronger life form just by running.
트럭커 성인은 달리는 것으로 보다 강한 전투 생명체로 자기 진화할 수 있지
Now, what will you do, Dagwon? Trucker Seijin's power isn't something ordinary!
자, 어쩔 테냐, 다그온 트럭커 성인의 힘은 만만치 않다구
Thunder Burn!
선더 번!
Electro Kick!
전기 킥!
Bolt Shoot!
볼트 슛!
How's that?!
어떠냐!
What?!
아니?!
Dammit!
젠장!
Magma Blast!
마그마 블래스트!
Power Dagwon!
파워 다그온!
Hmph. I won't lose in a match of power!
흥, 파워 승부라면 지지 않는다!
Power Tank Mode!
파워 탱크 모드!
My turn!
이번엔 나다!
Thunder Slash!
선더 슬러시!
What?!
아니?!
Ryu!
류!
Shadow Kunai!
섀도우 쿠나이!
Senpai!
선배!
We must stop this right now!
어서 이녀석을 멈춰야 해!
Is this it?
이건가?
I'll leave the rest to you, Rai!
뒤는 네게 맡기마, 라이!
Yes, sir!
네!
Come here, Thunder Shuttle!
Come here, 선더 셔틀
Thunder Fusion!
뇌명합체
(雷鳴合體)
Thunder Dagwon!
선더 다그온
Thunder Lancer!
선더 랜서!
Good job, Thunder Dagwon.
훌륭하다, 선더 다그온
Yes, sir!
네!
You do pretty well, Dagwon.
꽤 하는군, 다그온
But still...
하지만 말이다
You aren't going to be so happy later on!
기뻐하는 것도 지금 뿐이다
Good morning, everyone!
여러분 안녕하세요~
Let's study as much as we can!
오늘도 힘차게 공부합시다~
Sheesh, Rai is always so motivated.
아아~ 라이 군은 의욕이 넘치는구만
It seems that Rai was so happy to be praised by Ryu.
라이도 참… 류에게 칭찬받은 게 무척이나 기뻤나 보네요
M- Ms. Maria!
마, 마리아 씨…!
Rai, you know what you did wrong yesterday!
라이… 어제는 큰일이었단 말이야!
Why did you do that to us, Rai?
너무해, 라이
Why did you left us in such a place?
그런 곳에 두고 가 버리다니…
I'm sorry!
죄송합니다
I'll compensate you by any means however I can!
제가 할 수 있는 게 있다면 그 어떤 보상이라도…
That's great!
그래!
Then help me with the experiment of bending spoons!
그럼 숟가락 구부리기 실험을 도와줘
Rai, don't be so optimistic!
라이, 우쭐해하지 마라
Oh, senpai!
아, 선배…
Hmph, what's so great about bending spoons?
흥, 숟가락 따위를 구부리는 걸 가지고 말이야
I can bend a steel pipe!
난 철 파이프를…
Look, how's this?
봐라, 이런 거다
That's my senpai!
과연 선배!
As you see, it's awesome!
어떠냐, 훌륭하지?
Ms. Maria!
마리아 씨
I'll happily become the test subject instead of Rai!
라이 대신 제가 기꺼이 실험 대상이 되겠습니다
I'm sorry, but please get out of here.
미안하지만, 비켜주지 않을래?
Huh?
하아?
She's saying, Geki isn't needed!
그러니까, 게키는 필요없다는 거지
N-no way...
그, 그럴수가…
Rai!
라이!
Stop right there, Rai!
기다려, 라이!
Please let me go!
이제 그만 봐주세요~
The sun suddenly called me
태양이 갑작스레 나를 불러내서
taiyou ga fui ni ore wo izanau
To come to the blue sea
푸르게 비치는 바다로 만나러 갔지
aoku sukitooru umi ni ai ni kita
The ripples are coming and going
밀려왔다 돌아가는 잔물결
yosete wa kaesu sazanami
An endless melody
멈추지 않는 멜로디
tomaru koto nai MELODY
To keep that shape for eternity
그 모습을 영원히 유지할 수 있도록
sono sugata towa ni tsunagu you ni
I'll follow the fate of the dream
꿈의 행방을 뒤쫓아 갈 거야
oikakete yuku yo yume no yukue
Sparkling far away
멀리서 반짝이던
tooku kirameita
A Prism in the Wind
바람 속의 프리즘
kaze no naka no PRISM
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Preview for Next Episode
용자지령
다그온
차회예고
Hido took down Ryu?! He went down, not resisting at all?!
류가 히도 따위에게…! 저항 한 번 못 하고 쓰러지다니!
What's going on, Ryu senpai?! Why aren't you fighting back?!
어떻게 된 겁니까, 류 선배! 어째서 반격하지 않는 겁니까?!
Meanwhile, an alien named Shura is targeting a mysterious girl, Minako.
한편, 우주인 슈라가 노리는 신비한 소녀 미나코
Does she truly have the ability of foresight? And why did Brave Seijin appear?
그녀는 정말 예지 능력자일까요? 그리고 브레이브 성인이 나타난 목적은?!
It's full of mysteries!
으아아~ 전부 수수께끼다!
Next time on Yuusha Shirei Dagwon! The Revival of White Wings
다음회 용자지령 다그온
부활의 하얀 날개
That machine is flying upon the sky once again!
그 머신이… 또다시 드넓은 하늘에 날아오른다!
White Wings of Resurrection
부활의 하얀 날개